Roy Justus Papers
Roy Justus Papers
- Printed material
  - International clippings, 1951; 1955,; 1957 (Box 1)
  - Judge magazine, Apr 9 1921 (Box 8)
  - Letters to the Editor, 1954-1966; 1968 (Box 8)
  - Minneapolis Star Journal and Tribune tintypes, circa 1940s (Box 1)
  - Poster for Illinois Committee National Service Fund of Disabled American Veterans, undated (Map-case 1, Drawer 107)
  - Proofs, undated; negatives (Oversize 1)
  - Proofs, 1965; undated; annual year end retrospective (Oversize 1)
  - Miscellaneous, 1954; 1958,; 1961 (Box 1)
- Miscellaneous
  - Caption indexes, alphabetical, with dates, supplied by donor, not verified for accuracy; encompasses cover cartoons from the 1940s-1970s; 2 binders (Box 8)
  - "The Great Challenge" exhibition, circa 1958 (Box 8)
  - Idea notes from Justus' desk, undated (Box 8)